Guide to the Stewart O'Nan papers, 1987-2009.
O'Nan, Stewart papers
- Series XI. The Circus Fire
  - Subseries XI e. Media
    - Mordas, Mahoney, Kearns, Teffs, J Pearse, G Pearse, TR-9279 (Box 27)
    - G Pearse, Joan Rivers, John Stewart Jr., TR-9280 (Box 27)
    - Unlabelled, TR-9281-TR-9289 (Box 27)
    - D. Cook 1, TR-9290 (Box 27)
    - D. Cook 2, TR-9291 (Box 27)
    - CBS World Tonight Story 40th Anniversary Ceremony, July 6, 1984; TR-9292 (Box 27)
    - Jerry Stepakoff and parents on the Circus Fire, 1998; TR-9293 (Box 27)
    - Circus Fire: Nan Glass, West Hartford Town Clerk, june 19, 1984; TR-9294 (Box 27)
    - Circus Fire: Wayne Camillieri, City Councilman, June 8, 1984; TR-9295 (Box 27)
    - circus Fire: John Stewart, Fire Chief, June 19, 1984; TR-9296 (Box 27)
    - Eunice Groark, May 24, 1984; TR-9297 (Box 27)
    - Joseph Faulise, Lt. Governor, June 12, 1984; TR-9298 (Box 27)
    - Charlie Barr, Allied Florists Assn., June 6, 1984; TR-9299 (Box 27)
    - Donald Anderson, June 21, 1984; TR-9300 (Box 27)
    - Morris Handler, June 12, 1984; TR-9301 (Box 27)
    - William Cieri, Retired Fire Captain, May 29, 1984; TR-9302 (Box 27)
    - William Mortensen, Former Mayor, June 12, 1984; TR-9303 (Box 27)
    - "Someone yelled fire" WPOP, 1984; TR-9304 (Box 27)
    - Circus Marches, TR-9305 (Box 27)
    - The Hartford Circus Fire, TR-9306 (Box 27)
    - Circus Favorites, TR-9307 (Box 27)
    - Audio book, 4 tapes, TR-9310 (Box 27)
    - Audio book, unabridged, 7 tapes, TR-9311 (Box 27)
    - The Heritage Circus Band, CD-1646 (Box 27)
- Series XII. Everyday People
  - Subseries XII a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Rough Daily Draft Pages, September 1997-April 1998 (Box 30)
    - 2 Boxed MS, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Bound MS (Box 31)
    - White boxed MS copy of final draft version, July 17 2000 (Box 30)
    - Bound MS Original draft version, July 17 2000 (Box 29)
    - Bound MS (Box 29)
    - MS (Box 29)
    - MS Copyedits (Box 29)
    - Boxed MS original, April 16, 1998 (Box 29)
    - Bound MS with many notes (Box 29)
    - Bound MS copy with revisions in green ink, July 1, 1998 (Box 29)
    - Bound MS (Box 29)
    - Loose MS audio abridgement (Box 30)
    - Bound MS Ink revisions (Box 30)
  - Subseries XII b. Research/Notes
    - Sources (Box 28)
    - Notes (Box 30)
    - Daily Journal, September 1997-April 1998 (Box 31)
    - Notes and notebook on Everyday People and other (Box 31)
    - Interviews (Box 31)
    - Notes (Box 31)
  - Subseries XII c. Miscellaneous
    - Books by Billy (Box 28)
    - Magazines (Box ?)
    - Maps (Box ?)
    - Creative non-fiction with "My Mysteries of Pittsburgh" (Box 31)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 52)
- Series XIII. Summer People
  - Subseries XIII a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Boxed MS (Box 29)
    - Bound MS (Box 29)
    - Boxed MS edited, July 26, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Loose MS (Box 31)
    - Raw Daily Draft pages (Box 32)
    - Boxed MS (Box 33)
    - Boxed MS original revised, February 20, 2001 (Box 33)
    - Revision notes, A. Manette Ansay, January 2001 (Box 33)
    - Bound MS Revisions in Ink (Box 33)
    - Bound MS inscribed to Trudy, September 2000 (Box 33)
    - Revision notes from Lamar Herrin (Box 34)
    - Bound MS Revision copy, April 2001 (Box 34)
  - Subseries XIII b. Research/Notes
    - Research on photography and Chautauqua (Box 33)
    - Notes, Summer 2000 (Box 33)
    - Notes (Box 33)
    - Notes and research materials on characters, Chautauqua, septic systems (Box 33)
    - Notes on Research (Box 34)
    - Daily Journal Summer People/Wish You Were Here, September 1999-July 2001 (Box 34)
  - Subseries XIII c. Miscellaneous
    - Notes from bulletin board (Box 33)
    - Editorial Notes from Brendan Cahill, July 17, 2001 (Box 34)
- Series XIV. Wish You Were Here
  - Subseries XIV a. Manuscript Drafts
    - 3 Bound MS (Box 31)
    - Loose MS (Box 31)
    - Boxed MS final revised MS, edits on top of Brendan Cahill's., July 26, 2001 (Box 32)
    - MS Copy edits (Box 32)
    - MS Copyedit, April 2001 (Box 34)
  - Subseries XIV b. Research/Notes
    - Photographs (Box 32)
    - Notebook- travel and random notes (Box 34)
    - Reviews, publicity, and tour information (Box 52)
  - Subseries XIV c. Correspondence
    - Blurb Correspondence, February 2002 (Box 32)
- Series XV. The Night Country
  - Subseries XV a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Boxed raw daily draft pages with notes, Fall 2000-Spring 2001 (Box 35)
    - Bound MS (Box 34)
    - Boxed MSS two bound copies (Box 34)
    - Bound MS revision copy, June 14, 2002 (Box 35)
    - 2 Loose MS revised, June 2002 (Box 35)
    - Bound MS new review copy with notes from Jenny Egan, May 17, 2002 (Box 34)
    - Bound MS review copy, February 14, 2002 (Box 34)
    - Bound MS Three copies, June 2002 (Box 35)
    - 6 MS pass drafts with edits (Box 36)
    - Two Bound MS, August 2002 (Box 35)
    - Loose MS, August 2002 (Box 35)
    - Loose MS Original, August 2002 (Box 35)
    - Bound MS revision copy, July 7, 2001 (Box 34)
    - Loose MS Revision Original, October 22, 2001 (Box 35)
    - Bound MS Revision Copy, October 22, 2001 (Box 35)
    - Loose MS clean first draft, July 6, 2001 (Box 35)
    - 2 Loose MS (Box 36)
  - Subseries XV b. Research
    - Bulletin board notes (Box 36)
    - Stray notes (Box 36)
    - Accident Report Files (Box 36)
    - Working Journal, October 2000-October 2001 (Box 36)
    - Notes (Box 36)
  - Subseries XV c. Miscellaneous
    - Promo flyer (Box 34)
    - Audio release, July 2003 (Box 34)
    - Audio Abridgement (Box 34)
    - Publicity, catalog and tour documents (Box 36)
    - German Translation notes, January 2003 (Box 36)
    - Avon accident notes and research (Box 36)
    - O'Nan essay drafts (Box 36)
  - Subseries XV d. Correspondence
    - Letters from Rick Moody, Paul Cody, Lamar Herrin, Luis Urrea (Box 36)
    - Correspondence with Farrar, Strauss and Giroux (Box 36)
    - Letters and emails from Theodore Weesner, Peter Sraub, Rick Moody, Jonathan Lethem, Luis Urrea, Michael Martone, Dennis Lehane, Elizabeth Graver, Chris Offutt, Jennifer Egan, and others (Box 36)
    - Correspondence with FSG (Box 36)
- Series XVI. Upstate / The Good Wife
  - Subseries XVI a. Manuscript Drafts
    - MSS drafts dead matter (Box 38)
    - MS 1st pass master, October 2005 (Box 39)
    - MS 1st pass author, August 2004 (Box 39)
    - MS 2nd pass author, October 2005 (Box 39)
    - MS 2nd pass master, October 2004 (Box 39)
    - 1st pass queries, September 2004 (Box 41)
    - MS copy edits, September 2004 (Box 41)
    - Bound MS with loose revision pages and editorial letters, November 2003 (Box 41)
    - MS 2nd Pass author (Box 41)
    - 2 Boxed MS Original, July 6, 2003 (Box 39)
    - Boxed MS copy, July 6, 2003 (Box 39)
    - Bound MS copy of original (Box 39)
    - Bound MS (Box 39)
    - Raw daily draft with notes (Box 40)
    - Boxed MS original revised, October 2003 (Box 41)
    - Bound MS revision copy with minor revisions in ink (Box 41)
    - Bound MS (Box 41)
  - Subseries XVI b. Research
    - Tioga County Courier, January-April 2002 (Box 38)
    - Tioga County Courier, May-August 2002 (Box 38)
    - Tioga County Courier, September-December 2002 (Box 38)
    - Tioga County Courier, January-April 2003 (Box 38)
    - Tioga County Courier, May-August 2003 (Box 38)
    - Notes (Box 38)
    - The Moonlighter, July 2002 (Box 38)
    - Magazines/Published Material (Box 38)
    - Photographs (Box 38)
    - Chicken Soup for the Prisoner's Soul ed. by Jack Canfield, Mark Victor Hansen, Tom Lagana, 2000 (Box 38)
    - You Are Going to Prison by Jim Hogshire, 1999 (Box 38)
    - Disguised as a Poem by Judith Tannenbaum, 2000 (Box 38)
    - Behind the Walls: A Guide for Families and Friends of Texas Prison Inmates by Jorge Antonio Renaud, 2002 (Box 38)
    - Undoing Time ed. by Jeff Evans, 2001 (Box 38)
    - Doing Time ed. by Bell Gale Chevigny, 1999 (Box 38)
    - Prison Diary by Edward Conway, 1977 (Box 38)
    - Outsiders Looking In: How to Keep from Going Crazy When Someone You Love Goes to Jail by Toni Weymouth and Maria Telesco, 1998 (Box 38)
    - Prisoners of Love by TK Cyan-Brock (Box 38)
    - Tioga County Courier, November 2003 (Box 41)
    - Notes (Box 40)
    - Research Materials: Parole, Auburn Material, Prison life, Clinton, Bare Hill, Maps, Courts, some correspondence. (Box 40)
    - Bulletin Board notes, November 2003 (Box 41)
    - Bulletin Board notes, September 2003 (Box 41)
    - Post first draft notes (Box 41)
    - Tioga County Couriers (Box 41)
    - Loose notes (Box 41)
    - Notebook working journal, November 2001-November 2003 (Box 41)
  - Subseries XVI c. Miscellaneous
    - Beyond Bars/No Extended Embraces, 2000; V-5969 (Box 27)
    - Publicity and Reviews (Box 41)
  - Subseries XVI d. Correspondence
    - Correspondence with FSG, April 2004-October 2004 (Box 41)
    - Fleetwood Mac Permissions Correspondence, August 2004 (Box 41)
    - Editorial back and forth, October 2003 (Box 41)
    - Feedback including Stephen King, Paul Cody, Lamar Herrin, Luis Urrea (Box 41)
- Series XVII. Faithful
  - Subseries XVII a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Loose MS with emails from Stephen King, February-November 2004 (Box 41)
    - MS Partial, single spaced (Box 41)
    - Raw daily draft pages, February-November 2004 (Box 63)
    - Loose earlier partial drafts and editorial notes, February -August 2004 (Box 43)
    - 2 Raw daily draft pages (Box 43)
    - MS 2nd pass page proofs, November 2004 (Box 44)
    - 1st pass page proofs, November 2004 (Box 43)
    - Missing pages, November 8, 2004 (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous copyedited MS pages (4 sets), November 2004 (Box 43)
  - Subseries XVII b. Research/Notes
    - The Official Rules of Baseball: An Anecdotal Look at the Rules of Baseball and How They Came to Be by David Nemec, 1994 (Box 42)
    - Summer of '49 by David Halberstam, 1989 (Box 42)
    - The Umpire Strikes Back by Ron Luciano and David Fisher, 1982 (Box 42)
    - The Boys of Summer by Roger Kahn, 1971 (Box 42)
    - Henry Wiggen's Books by Mark Harris, 1953 (Box 42)
    - Surviving Grady by Tom McCarney and Tom Deady, two copies, 2004 (Box 42)
    - Five Seasons: A Baseball Companion by Roger Angell's, 1978 (Box 42)
    - Newspapers, clippings and notes, March-June 2004 (Box 42)
    - Newspapers and notes (Box 43)
    - Summer game notes and program, 2004 (Box ?)
    - Autographed photo of Bobby M. Jones (Box ?)
    - Loose notes (Box 43)
    - Daily journal notebook (Box 42)
  - Subseries XVII c. Miscellaneous
    - 12 Major League game baseballs caught at Fenway Park (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 44)
    - Drew Gallager Correspondence with large gloss copy of Carlton Ernest Fisk Hall of Fame Induction Day card (Box 51)
  - Subseries XVII d. Media
    - NESN Red Sox Preview, March 29, 2004; V-5962 (Box 27)
    - Steve's First Pitch, March 3, 2003; V-5963 (Box 27)
    - Sox win World Series, V-5964 (Box 27)
    - Sox win World Series 2, V-5965 (Box 27)
    - "Butterfingers" Director's Cut, V-5966 (Box 27)
    - Johnny on Letterman, V-5967 (Box 27)
    - Sox World Series Parade, V-5968 (Box 27)
    - 2 copies "The Book Show", 2007; CD-1645 (Box 27)
- Series XVIII. Last Night at the Lobster
  - Subseries XVIII a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Early raw draft pages (Box 44)
    - Bound MS copy, November 9, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Loose MS, December 2 2006 (Box 44)
    - Various Loose MS pages (Box 44)
    - Loose MS, November 9, 2005 (Box 44)
    - 2 copies Bound MS (Box 44)
    - MS pages (Box 44)
    - Boxed MS 1 bound, 2 loose copies (Box 44)
    - MS copyedited, January 2007 (Box 44)
    - Design pages (Box 44)
  - Subseries XVIII b. Research/Notes
    - Menus, Coasters (Box 44)
    - Photographs (Box 44)
    - Notes (Box 44)
    - Notes, photos, emails from Paul Cody, Elizabeth Holmes, Lamat Herrin (Box 44)
    - Working Journal, April-October 2005 (Box ?)
    - Loose notes (Box 44)
    - Notes in Binder (Box 44)
    - Interview with John Reeman (Box 44)
    - Viking catalog (Box 44)
    - German catalog (Box 44)
  - Subseries XVIII c. Correspondence
    - Editorial letter from Josh Kendall (Box 44)
    - Emails from Sung J. Woo and Susan Straight (Box 44)
    - Letter from Lowry Pei (Box 44)
    - Emails from Pete Duval, James McConkey, Dennis Lehane (Box 44)
    - German Translation correspondence, March 2007 (Box 44)
    - Email from Susan Straight, February 2006 (Box 44)
  - Subseries XVIII d. Miscellaneous
    - Publicity, correspondence and reviews (Box 44)
- Series XIX. Songs for the Missing / Since You've Been Gone / Somewhere over the Rainbow / About a Girl
  - Subseries XIX a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Boxed MS, January 2008 (Box 45)
    - Bound MS (Box 45)
    - Bound MS with new later chapters (Box 45)
    - Boxed MS post copy edits, February 2008 (Box 45)
    - MS draft (Box 45)
    - Bound MS two copies (Box 45)
    - Boxed MS Original, October 17, 2006 (Box 45)
    - Bound MS 3 copies (Box 46)
    - Raw Daily Draft pages, 2006 (Box 46,47)
    - Boxed MS Original, April 2007 (Box 45)
    - Bound MS with ink revisions (Box 46)
    - MSS in binder including folder with draft of final section (Box 46)
    - Bound MSS 3 copies, March 2007 (Box 46)
    - Boxed MS, December 2006 (Box 46)
    - 1st pass with correspondence (Box 46)
  - Subseries XIX b. Research/Notes
    - Maps and notes (Box 45)
    - Notebook, 2005-2006 (Box 45)
    - Phone books, book (Lena) (Box 47)
    - Notes in folders: Organization, missing, crazy lady search, maps, research, clippings, funerals, search procedures (Box 47)
  - Subseries XIX c. Correspondence
    - Emails from Luis Urrea, Lowry Pei, Paul Cody, Lamar Herrin (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 46)
  - Subseries XIX d. Miscellaneous
    - Acknowledgements catalog copy (Box 45)
    - Andrew Ervin's correspondence, notes, and a draft MS of "The Phillie Phanatic" authored by him, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Test cover on Sandra Dallas' "Alice's Tulips" (Box 46)
- Series XX. Clara (Screenplay)
  - Subseries XX a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Notes and draft pages, 1997-1998 (Box 48)
    - 2 loose MS (Box 48)
    - Paper-clipped MS pages (Box 48)
    - Loose MS pages (Box 48)
    - Bound MS with A. Manette Ansay's changes and letter, August 1997 (Box 47)
    - MS, August 1997 (Box 48)
    - Bound MS, 2 copies (Box 47)
    - Boxed MS, August 5, 1997 (Box 48)
    - Rough MS pages (Box 48)
  - Subseries XX b. Research/Notes
    - Loose Notes (Box 48)
    - Working journal for Clara, Lie Down in Darkness, stories and Vietnam Reader essays; also has MS copies of stories "Monsters" and "The Great Rushdie" in pocket, 1997 (Box 47)
    - Biography of Clara Schumann, by Nancy Reich (Box 47)
  - Subseries XX c. Correspondence
    - Notes from A. Manette Ansay (Box 47)
- Screenplays by O'Nan and Other Authors
  - Subseries XXI a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Stanley Kubrick's and Diane Johnson's treatment of "The Shining" (Box 48)
    - Bound MS screenplay of William Styron's "Lie Down in Darkness" (Box 48)
    - Rough MS Pages "Lie Down in Darkness" (Box 49)
    - The Challenger (Box 48)
    - MS Flannery O'Connor's "The Violent Bear It Away", January 1993 (Box 48)
    - MS "The Violent Bear It Away" with screenplay of Tim O'Brien's "Going After Cacciato" (Box 48)
    - Two MS "Going After Cacciato" (Box 48)
    - Two MS "Going after Cacciato" (Box 49)
    - MS "The Violent Bear it Away" (Box 48)
    - MS Screenplay Denis Johnson's "Angels" (Box 48)
    - MS Angels three copies (Box 48)
    - Loose MS "Angels", May 1994 (Box 48)
    - MS "Poe" original screenplay (Box 48)
    - MS Poe work draft, October 1995 (Box 48)
    - Various loose draft pages, including Monsters, the Departed, and Out There (Box 49)
    - Bound MS "20 Burgers" (Box 49)
    - Drafts "20 Burgers" (Box 49)
    - "The Ghost Ship" daily draft pages, Spring 2004 (Box 49)
    - "My Mysteries of Pittsburgh" Draft of essay (Box 50)
    - "The Departed" Draft (Box 50)
    - Bound MSS "The Hummingbird's Daughter" Luis Urrea (Box 51)
    - Bound Script "Southern Comfort" (Box 51)
    - Bound MS "7 Days and 7 Sins" Pamela Ditchoff (Box 51)
    - MS from Lowry Pei, Deidre Pope. M. Kelby, Debbie Waldman (Box 51)
    - Poe story draft (Box 51)
    - Drafts of Non-fiction pieces and book reviews: The Lost World of Richard Yates (including research) (Box 51)
    - Early draft of children's story "St. Patrick and the Snake" (Box 51)
    - Bound MS "House of the Deaf" by Lamar Herrin (Box 52)
    - Screenplay of "The Night Country" Niall Johnson (Box 53)
    - "When Black is Burned" Andrew Malan Wilward (Box 53)
    - MS photocopied paranoid outsider art project/cry for help from unbalanced man (Box 53)
    - MS Paul Tremblay "Swallowing a Donkey's Eye" (Box 53)
    - Boxed MS "Who He Was" Paul Cody (Box 53)
    - Drafts/correspondence with other authors (Box 53)
    - Boxed MS "Hollow Ground" Stephen Marion (Box ?)
    - "Giovanna's 86 Circles and Other Stories" Paola Corso (Box 53)
    - Boxed MS "Cowbird" Stephen Marion (Box 53)
    - Screenplays from International Creative Management, Inc.: Law and Order, Six Feet Under, NYPD Blue, The Heart Department, Law and Order: Criminal Intent, 24, Alias, The Barn (Box 55)
    - On Writers and Writing by John Gardiner, ed. Stewart O'Nan, 1994 (Box 60)
  - Subseries XXI b. Research/Notes
    - Notecards and notes for screen treatment of John Edgar Widemen's "The Lynchers" (Box 48)
    - "Going after Cacciato" notebook and notes (Box 49)
    - "In the Walled City" notes (Box 49)
    - Old notes (Box 55)
    - Old notebooks and journals, 1985-1989 (Box 55-57)
  - Subseries XXI c. Miscellaneous
    - "Poe" Documents and notes (Box 48)
    - On Writers and Writing publication correspondence (Box 49)
    - Poe project list (Box ?)
    - ATTU correspondence, landscape photos (Box 51)
    - "The Ghost Ship" Bulletin boards notes, notes, research, March 2004 (Box 49)
    - Kennywood: Roller Coaster Capital of the World by Charles Jacques, Jr. (Box 49)
    - Amusement Park by Robert Stuart Nathan (Box 49)
    - "The Ghost Ship" Reviews and publicity, notebooks, letters from Lisa Fugard and Nick Flynn (Box ?)
    - Non-fiction essays, reviews, corresponding letters, occasional journalism and essays (mostly op-ed for German papers) (Box 50)
    - Book reviews and publicity: NY Times, Atlantic Monthly, "Home is the Exile", Pittsburgh Post-Gazette (Box 50)
    - German Publications, essays, correspondence with magazines, publicity (Box 50)
    - Letters Mick Cochrane and Rita Ciresi (Box ?)
    - Travel and Workshop documents- Circus Fire (Box 51)
    - Henry Dax correspondence and photographs (Box 51)
    - 2004 National Book Award Program (Box 51)
    - The 55th National Book Awards program (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 51)
    - 2004 Conneticut Book Award Papers (Box 51)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 52)
    - Correspondence with publishers (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous drafts, correspondence, notes, research (Box 52)
    - 2004 National Book Award fiction panel (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous reviews, publicity and literary mementos: Borrowers Ball, Granta, book fairs, programs, catalogs (Box 53)
    - Reviews in magazines, Newspapers (Box 54)
    - Certificate of appreciation from the Ruth Rockwood Memorial Library (Box 54)
    - Literary Magazines with O'Nan pieces (Box 54)
    - Lowry Pei "Never Let You Go" (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous MS short stories (Box 54)
    - 2001 NEA Fiction Panel submissions (Box 54)
    - Luis Urrea "The Hummingbird's Daughter" (Box 55)
    - Adam Braver "Mr. Lincoln's Wars" (Box 55)
    - Tom Piazza "My Cold War" (Box 55)
    - William Gay "Provinces of Night" (Box 54)
    - A Manette Ansay "Midnight Champagne" (Box 55)
    - Publicity, catalogs, miscellaneous correspondence (Box 55)
    - Literary Memorabilia: name tags, programs (Box 55)
    - WNYC Stewart O'Nan, TR-9308 (Box 27)
    - WHCU Stewart O'Nan/Casey Stevens, March 1996; TR-9309 (Box 27)
    - Stewart O'Nan: Die Speed Queen (Germany), 1998; V-5960 (Box 27)
    - PA Miners' Story, V-5961 (Box 27)
    - Contracts and royalty statement correspondence and documents: Borchardt, Royal Gernet (Box 56)
    - Box of old rejection slips from literary magazines (Box 56)
- Series XXII. Miscellaneous/ Works by Other Authors
  - Subseries XXII a.Manuscript Drafts
    - Miscellaneous drafts (Box 49)
    - Tribeca Productions (Box 49)
    - "Goats: The Animated Short" by Jonathan Rosenberg (Box 49)
    - Brian James Freeman "The Suicide Diary" Draft, 2007 (Box 59)
    - Christopher Torckio "The Truth at Daybreak" draft, October 2007 (Box 58)
    - Robert Swartwood "The Dishonored Dead" signed draft (Box 59)
    - Paul Tremblay "The Little Sleep" draft (Box 58)
    - Ross Raisin "Out Backward" draft (Box 59)
    - Holly Robinson "The Gerbil Farmer's Daughter", 2009 (Box 59)
    - "SOFTWAR" play script by Sung J. Woo, story by O'Nan, March 19, 2007 (Box 59)
    - Jefferson Davis novel by Lamar Herrin (Box 59)
    - Raymond Miller, "The Scent of Blood" Published version, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Peter Schilling Jr "The End of Baseball" advance uncorrected proof, May 2 2008 (Box 59)
    - Unidentified draft signed "Bill", May 31 2008 (Box 59)
    - Willie Vlautin "Northline", October 9, 2007 (Box 59)
  - Subseries XXII b. Miscellaneous
    - Loose notes (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991-2002 (Box 49)
    - Drue Heinz Award, 2001 (Box 49)
    - Drue Heinz Award booklet, 2001 (Box 62)
    - Editions de L'Olivier (Box 49)
    - Gernert Company clippings (Box 49)
    - Guggenheim Foundation application (Box 49)
    - Henry Holt and Company Correspondence (Box 49)
    - Horror Writers Association Newsletter, 1999 (Box 49)
    - Moore Literary Agency documents (Box 49)
    - 5 photos of O'Nan, one of a house (Box 49)
    - O'Nan Interview, September 11, 1997 (Box 49)
    - Lamar Herrin Interview (Box 49)
    - Other authors book fliers and pamphlets, October 10, 1991 (Box 49)
    - Don Delillo Newspaper Clippings (Box 49)
    - Other authors shorts: Natasha Cohen, Charlotte Herbert, Susan Williams, Sung Woo, Steve Houston MA thesis, Joanna Scott, A. Manette Ansay (Vinegar Hill, Midnight Champagne) (Box 50)
    - New York Times Magazine, July 27, 1997 (Box 50)
    - Black Warrior Review photocopy and letter (Box 50)
    - Various Publications (Box 50)
    - E-2C Plane photographs and negatives (Box 50)
    - Memo books, 1992-1993 (Box 50)
    - Record book on readings, 1984-1993 (Box 50)
    - Author Visits flyers (Box 50)
    - Travel and Workshop information: Hartford writers, National Endowment for the Arts, Borrowers Ball, Canisius College, Neiman Conference, OK Best, National Writers Workshop (Box 50)
    - Joanne Moody, drawings from students, 2001 (Box 51)
    - Leipzig information, 2001 (Box 51)
    - Drew O'Brien letter (Box 51)
    - Pen American Center application, child's drawing of Y2K (Box 51)
    - The Thousand-Mile War by Brian Garfield (Box 51)
    - Mine all Mine by Adam Davies, 2 copies, one to O'Nan one to S. King., 2008 (Box 59)
    - Numbering Stars by Charlotte Hebert, 2006 (Box 59)
    - The Double Dealer Redux, 1998 (Box 59)
    - Rubber letter to Billie Jean King, 1973 (Box 59)
    - My Life in Heavy Metal by Steve Almond, 2002 (Box 59)
    - Something More by Lowry Pei (Box 59)
    - Pagan Time by Micah Perks (Box 59)
    - Hollow Ground by Stephen Marion (Box 59)
    - The Wooden Sea by Jonathan Carroll (Box 59)
    - Blood Acre by Peter Landesman, 2000 (Box 60)
    - Here in the World Victoria Lancelotta (Box 60)
    - Barbara Robinette Moss "Change me into Zeus' Daughter" (Box 60)
    - Robert Bingham "Pure Slaughter Value" (Box 60)
    - Kim Barnes "Hungry for the World", 2000 (Box 60)
    - Brett Savory "Fright Night" (Box 60)
    - Cartoon print (Box 60)
    - Brett Savory and Gord Zajac "The Distance Travelled: A Little Slice of Heaven" (Box 60)